{
  "uniqueId": 31,
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "an ardent early supporter of a cause or reform",
      "answer": "apostle"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking kindness",
      "answer": "unkind"
    },
    {
      "question": "a personal journal (as a physical object)  ",
      "answer": "diary"
    },
    {
      "question": "be on one's guard",
      "answer": "beware"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being unduly vain and conceited",
      "answer": "conceit"
    },
    {
      "question": "to make grasping motions",
      "answer": "snatch"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of lacking courage  ",
      "answer": "cowardice"
    },
    {
      "question": "a police officer of the lowest rank  ",
      "answer": "constable"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking any definite plan or order or purpose",
      "answer": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "give by will, especially real property  ",
      "answer": "devise"
    },
    {
      "question": "pursue or chase relentlessly",
      "answer": "hound"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a halting and feeble manner",
      "answer": "feebly"
    },
    {
      "question": "impose something unpleasant",
      "answer": "inflict"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone whose occupation is catching fish  ",
      "answer": "fisherman"
    },
    {
      "question": "worry unnecessarily or excessively",
      "answer": "fuss"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to clergy not bound by monastic vows",
      "answer": "secular"
    },
    {
      "question": "fasten with buttons",
      "answer": "button"
    },
    {
      "question": "feel favorably disposed or willing",
      "answer": "incline"
    },
    {
      "question": "confidently optimistic and cheerful  ",
      "answer": "sanguine"
    },
    {
      "question": "the syllable naming the second (supertonic) note of any major scale in solmization  ",
      "answer": "re"
    },
    {
      "question": "without preparation or reflection",
      "answer": "blindly"
    },
    {
      "question": "accept or admit unwillingly  ",
      "answer": "grudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "the amount that many barrels might hold  ",
      "answer": "barrels"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activity of keeping something secret  ",
      "answer": "concealment"
    },
    {
      "question": "bluntly direct and outspoken but good-natured",
      "answer": "bluff"
    },
    {
      "question": "a coordinated outfit (set of clothing)  ",
      "answer": "ensemble"
    },
    {
      "question": "roll around the rim of",
      "answer": "rim"
    },
    {
      "question": "deserving of contempt or scorn  ",
      "answer": "contemptible"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to verbs in the imperative mood  ",
      "answer": "imperative"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to trot",
      "answer": "trot"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing consternation",
      "answer": "appalling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a workplace away from a studio at which some or all of a movie may be made",
      "answer": "location"
    },
    {
      "question": " unfamiliar",
      "answer": "new"
    },
    {
      "question": "a unit of weight equal to one sixteenth of a pound or 16 drams or 28.349 grams  ",
      "answer": "ounce"
    },
    {
      "question": "empty of liquid",
      "answer": "drain"
    },
    {
      "question": "more often or more frequently  ",
      "answer": "oftener"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a strong substantial way",
      "answer": "substantially"
    },
    {
      "question": "a deliberate pretense or exaggerated display  ",
      "answer": "affectation"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing lack of favoritism",
      "answer": "impartial"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by deep ill will",
      "answer": "poisonous"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is the first to think of or make something  ",
      "answer": "inventor"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Christianity) the act of mortifying the lusts of the flesh by self-denial and privation (especially by bodily pain or discomfort inflicted on yourself)  ",
      "answer": "mortification"
    },
    {
      "question": "get involved or mixed-up with",
      "answer": "mingle"
    },
    {
      "question": "get healthy again",
      "answer": "heal"
    },
    {
      "question": "not counterfeit or copied",
      "answer": "authentic"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of being overcome or subdued",
      "answer": "invincible"
    },
    {
      "question": "the person to whom you are engaged  ",
      "answer": "betrothed"
    },
    {
      "question": "attach to",
      "answer": "fasten"
    },
    {
      "question": "(mineralogy) two interwoven crystals that are mirror images on each other  ",
      "answer": "twins"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of excessive concern  ",
      "answer": "solicitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a significant degree",
      "answer": "materially"
    },
    {
      "question": "a notable achievement",
      "answer": "feat"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who believes and helps to spread the doctrine of another  ",
      "answer": "disciple"
    },
    {
      "question": "a messenger who bears or presents",
      "answer": "bearer"
    },
    {
      "question": "manipulate manually or in one's mind or imagination",
      "answer": "toy"
    },
    {
      "question": "high quality porcelain originally made only in China  ",
      "answer": "china"
    },
    {
      "question": "a unit of area (4840 square yards) used in English-speaking countries  ",
      "answer": "acre"
    },
    {
      "question": "be ignorant of or in the dark about  ",
      "answer": "ignore"
    },
    {
      "question": "a boat built by Noah to save his family and animals from the flood  ",
      "answer": "ark"
    },
    {
      "question": "a close observer",
      "answer": "spectator"
    },
    {
      "question": "an entrance that can be closed by a gate  ",
      "answer": "gateway"
    },
    {
      "question": "a girl or young woman who is unmarried  ",
      "answer": "lass"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing or experiencing dissatisfaction or restless longing",
      "answer": "discontented"
    },
    {
      "question": "use a bat",
      "answer": "bat"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of existing in reality",
      "answer": "subsistence"
    },
    {
      "question": "with respect to private feelings",
      "answer": "inwardly"
    },
    {
      "question": "consisting of fine particles",
      "answer": "powdered"
    },
    {
      "question": "extremely steep",
      "answer": "perpendicular"
    },
    {
      "question": "artist who composes or conducts music as a profession  ",
      "answer": "musician"
    },
    {
      "question": "exclusive control or possession of something",
      "answer": "monopoly"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing or made of or resembling or characteristic of a metal",
      "answer": "metallic"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an idle manner",
      "answer": "idly"
    },
    {
      "question": "trousers ending above the knee  ",
      "answer": "breeches"
    },
    {
      "question": "a facility composed of one or more pieces of equipment connected to or part of a structure and designed to provide a service such as heat or electricity or water or sewage disposal",
      "answer": "utility"
    },
    {
      "question": "deprive of parents  ",
      "answer": "orphan"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by order and planning",
      "answer": "systematic"
    },
    {
      "question": "beneath the surface of the earth",
      "answer": "underground"
    },
    {
      "question": "a single undivided natural thing occurring in the composition of something else",
      "answer": "unit"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing displeasure or anger  ",
      "answer": "frowning"
    },
    {
      "question": "device consisting of a piece of machinery",
      "answer": "mechanism"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a busy manner",
      "answer": "busily"
    },
    {
      "question": "stunned or confused and slow to react (as from blows or drunkenness or exhaustion)  ",
      "answer": "dazed"
    },
    {
      "question": "having undergone the Christian ritual of baptism  ",
      "answer": "baptized"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who seeks the advice of a lawyer  ",
      "answer": "client"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut or impressed into a surface",
      "answer": "engraved"
    },
    {
      "question": "constructed with or in the form of an arch or arches",
      "answer": "arched"
    },
    {
      "question": "a chronological account of events in successive years  ",
      "answer": "annals"
    },
    {
      "question": "a band of material around the waist that strengthens a skirt or trousers  ",
      "answer": "girdle"
    },
    {
      "question": "given to or characterized by presenting specious arguments",
      "answer": "plausible"
    },
    {
      "question": "exasperatingly difficult to handle or circumvent",
      "answer": "nasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "any supernatural being worshipped as controlling some part of the world or some aspect of life or who is the personification of a force  ",
      "answer": "deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "determined by earth's magnetic fields",
      "answer": "magnetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a medium brown to dark-brown color  ",
      "answer": "chocolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "falling short of some prescribed norm",
      "answer": "deficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "mentally disordered",
      "answer": "clouded"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of playing for stakes in the hope of winning (including the payment of a price for a chance to win a prize)",
      "answer": "gambling"
    },
    {
      "question": "the arrangement of spoken words alternating stressed and unstressed elements",
      "answer": "rhythm"
    },
    {
      "question": "examine (organs) for diagnostic purposes  ",
      "answer": "explore"
    },
    {
      "question": "constancy of tone or pitch or inflection  ",
      "answer": "monotony"
    },
    {
      "question": "put at a disadvantage",
      "answer": "disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "question": "igneous rock produced by eruption and solidified on or near the earth's surface",
      "answer": "volcanic"
    },
    {
      "question": "privileged treatment of a favored person or corporation (sometimes unethically)",
      "answer": "sweetheart"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ability to lead",
      "answer": "leadership"
    },
    {
      "question": "harass by imposing humiliating or painful tasks, as in military institutions  ",
      "answer": "haze"
    },
    {
      "question": "a narrative poem of popular origin  ",
      "answer": "ballad"
    },
    {
      "question": "dilute acetic acid  ",
      "answer": "vinegar"
    },
    {
      "question": "increased in extent or size or bulk or scope  ",
      "answer": "expanded"
    },
    {
      "question": "completely covered",
      "answer": "smothered"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of secluding yourself from others  ",
      "answer": "seclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "in proper order or sequence",
      "answer": "successively"
    },
    {
      "question": "rest one's weight on one's knees",
      "answer": "kneel"
    },
    {
      "question": "eat greedily",
      "answer": "devour"
    },
    {
      "question": "an attack calculated to draw enemy defense away from the point of the principal attack  ",
      "answer": "diversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of compensating for service or loss or injury  ",
      "answer": "recompense"
    },
    {
      "question": "a caretaker for an apartment house",
      "answer": "superintendent"
    },
    {
      "question": "immersing the body in water or sunshine  ",
      "answer": "bathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a hole into",
      "answer": "pierce"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being individual",
      "answer": "individuality"
    },
    {
      "question": "coat with plaster",
      "answer": "plaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "something apparently sensed but having no physical reality",
      "answer": "phantom"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or close in range to the highest natural adult male voice",
      "answer": "tenor"
    },
    {
      "question": "coming next after the twelfth in position  ",
      "answer": "thirteenth"
    },
    {
      "question": "bringing together military forces  ",
      "answer": "concentration"
    },
    {
      "question": "an intense desire for some particular thing  ",
      "answer": "craving"
    },
    {
      "question": "cry loudly, as of animals",
      "answer": "howl"
    },
    {
      "question": "strong feelings of embarrassment  ",
      "answer": "chagrin"
    },
    {
      "question": "measuring instrument for measuring temperature  ",
      "answer": "thermometer"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a degree exceeding normal or proper limits",
      "answer": "excessively"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who lives in a place",
      "answer": "liver"
    },
    {
      "question": "so as to be visible",
      "answer": "visibly"
    },
    {
      "question": "activity that refreshes and recreates",
      "answer": "refreshment"
    },
    {
      "question": "the post or function properly or customarily occupied or served by another",
      "answer": "stead"
    },
    {
      "question": "sterile member of a colony of social insects that forages for food and cares for the larvae  ",
      "answer": "worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "made neat and tidy by trimming",
      "answer": "trimmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "badly behaved",
      "answer": "naughty"
    },
    {
      "question": "covering or hiding",
      "answer": "concealing"
    },
    {
      "question": "an occasion for excessive eating or drinking",
      "answer": "bust"
    },
    {
      "question": "from on board a vessel into the water",
      "answer": "overboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "a male relative  ",
      "answer": "kinsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "returned for lack of funds",
      "answer": "rubber"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by a lightly pert and exuberant quality",
      "answer": "impertinent"
    },
    {
      "question": "(music) the section of a movement (especially in sonata form) where the major musical themes first occur  ",
      "answer": "exposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "coming next after the thirteenth in position  ",
      "answer": "fourteenth"
    },
    {
      "question": "having been taken in marriage  ",
      "answer": "wed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the yard associated with a church  ",
      "answer": "churchyard"
    },
    {
      "question": "lightness or fairness of complexion",
      "answer": "whiteness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of decorating a house or room  ",
      "answer": "furnishing"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by casual disrespect",
      "answer": "impudent"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing or making known",
      "answer": "revealing"
    },
    {
      "question": "with diligence",
      "answer": "diligently"
    },
    {
      "question": "a passageway through or under something, usually underground (especially one for trains or cars)",
      "answer": "tunnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to philosophy or philosophers",
      "answer": "philosophic"
    },
    {
      "question": "cook and serve on a plank",
      "answer": "plank"
    },
    {
      "question": "fly around",
      "answer": "whirl"
    },
    {
      "question": "an arena consisting of an oval or circular area enclosed by tiers of seats and usually covered by a tent",
      "answer": "circus"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of suffocating (someone) by constricting the windpipe",
      "answer": "choking"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or determined by psychology",
      "answer": "psychological"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking natural ease",
      "answer": "labored"
    },
    {
      "question": "any plant grown for its beauty or ornamental value  ",
      "answer": "ornamental"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by extravagance and profusion",
      "answer": "lavish"
    },
    {
      "question": "an uncomfortable feeling of mental painfulness or distress  ",
      "answer": "discomfort"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of stretching something tight",
      "answer": "tension"
    },
    {
      "question": "rough and crude",
      "answer": "robust"
    },
    {
      "question": "a situation in which people or things are crowded together",
      "answer": "crowding"
    },
    {
      "question": "tighten or fasten by means of screwing motions",
      "answer": "screw"
    },
    {
      "question": "scoop up or take up with a spoon",
      "answer": "spoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "pierce in order to draw a liquid from",
      "answer": "tap"
    },
    {
      "question": "not brought to an end or conclusion",
      "answer": "unfinished"
    },
    {
      "question": "an indication of radiant light drawn around the head of a saint  ",
      "answer": "aura"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of dressing and preparing yourself",
      "answer": "toilet"
    },
    {
      "question": "emotionally aroused  ",
      "answer": "stimulated"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of plants) capable of cross-fertilization or of being grafted  ",
      "answer": "congenial"
    },
    {
      "question": "sufficiently",
      "answer": "amply"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat with an agent",
      "answer": "dose"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring or falling between events or points in time",
      "answer": "intervening"
    },
    {
      "question": "has little chance of being the case or coming about",
      "answer": "unlikely"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit a ball so that it causes a backspin  ",
      "answer": "slice"
    },
    {
      "question": "given to haughty disregard of others  ",
      "answer": "cavalier"
    },
    {
      "question": "unaffected by self-interest  ",
      "answer": "disinterested"
    },
    {
      "question": "the qualities of a hero or heroine",
      "answer": "heroism"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sudden violent disturbance  ",
      "answer": "outburst"
    },
    {
      "question": "appear as though from hiding",
      "answer": "peep"
    },
    {
      "question": "a container (usually in a barn or stable) from which cattle or horses feed  ",
      "answer": "manger"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleasing and appropriate manner or style (especially manner or style of expression)  ",
      "answer": "felicity"
    },
    {
      "question": "find or declare guilty",
      "answer": "convict"
    },
    {
      "question": "reveal in private",
      "answer": "confide"
    },
    {
      "question": "crowded or massed together",
      "answer": "huddled"
    },
    {
      "question": "(postpositive) however",
      "answer": "though"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring once a month",
      "answer": "monthly"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt for whales  ",
      "answer": "whale"
    },
    {
      "question": "start to grow or develop",
      "answer": "bud"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a catalogue, compile a catalogue",
      "answer": "catalogue"
    },
    {
      "question": "food fish of warm Caribbean and Atlantic waters  ",
      "answer": "schoolmaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "aesthetically pleasing",
      "answer": "aesthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of acquiring something",
      "answer": "acquiring"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who lives in solitude  ",
      "answer": "hermit"
    },
    {
      "question": "avoiding embellishment or exaggeration (used for emphasis)",
      "answer": "literal"
    },
    {
      "question": "any unwholesome or desperate condition",
      "answer": "malady"
    },
    {
      "question": "be uncertain about",
      "answer": "puzzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "(ethnic slur) extremely offensive name for a Black person",
      "answer": "nigger"
    },
    {
      "question": "come together as in a cluster or flock",
      "answer": "cluster"
    },
    {
      "question": "reduced to silence",
      "answer": "silenced"
    },
    {
      "question": "reflecting light",
      "answer": "glistening"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a smooth and diplomatic manner",
      "answer": "smoothly"
    },
    {
      "question": "clothing in general",
      "answer": "apparel"
    },
    {
      "question": "filled with great numbers crowded together",
      "answer": "thronged"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or characteristic of an editor",
      "answer": "editorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "lasting for a markedly brief time",
      "answer": "fleeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "the termination or disintegration of a relationship (between persons or nations)  ",
      "answer": "dissolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of attacking an enemy  ",
      "answer": "offense"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disposition to be lenient in judging others",
      "answer": "softness"
    },
    {
      "question": "exchange or buy back for money",
      "answer": "ransom"
    },
    {
      "question": "spend a certain length of time",
      "answer": "sojourn"
    },
    {
      "question": "without a sound",
      "answer": "noiselessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "distinctly dissimilar or unlike",
      "answer": "diverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shrine where an oracular god is consulted  ",
      "answer": "oracle"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover the surface of",
      "answer": "paste"
    },
    {
      "question": "strife resulting from a lack of agreement  ",
      "answer": "discord"
    },
    {
      "question": "as hot as if in an oven  ",
      "answer": "baking"
    },
    {
      "question": "make into scrap or refuse",
      "answer": "scrap"
    },
    {
      "question": "cultivated since prehistoric times",
      "answer": "barley"
    },
    {
      "question": "be in a state of movement or action",
      "answer": "abound"
    },
    {
      "question": "exalted emotionally especially with pride  ",
      "answer": "uplifted"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel in an automobile  ",
      "answer": "automobile"
    },
    {
      "question": "in accord with rules and customs of a legislative or deliberative assembly",
      "answer": "parliamentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of decorating something (in the hope of making it more attractive)  ",
      "answer": "decoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "a workman who fulls (cleans and thickens) freshly woven cloth for a living  ",
      "answer": "fuller"
    },
    {
      "question": "coming next after the nineteenth in position  ",
      "answer": "twentieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "a painful inflammation of the big toe and foot caused by defects in uric acid metabolism resulting in deposits of the acid and its salts in the blood and joints  ",
      "answer": "gout"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to the territory of any state or ruler",
      "answer": "territorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of liquids) clouded as with sediment",
      "answer": "cloudy"
    },
    {
      "question": "agriculture considered as an occupation or way of life",
      "answer": "farming"
    },
    {
      "question": "(pathology) not presently active",
      "answer": "latent"
    },
    {
      "question": "adorned with tongues of flame  ",
      "answer": "inflamed"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used as intensives) extremely",
      "answer": "madly"
    },
    {
      "question": "creating thread  ",
      "answer": "spinning"
    },
    {
      "question": "having an intended meaning altered or misrepresented",
      "answer": "distorted"
    },
    {
      "question": "authorize by certificate  ",
      "answer": "certificate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dark cell (usually underground) where prisoners can be confined  ",
      "answer": "dungeon"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disturbance that is extremely disruptive",
      "answer": "earthquake"
    },
    {
      "question": "a penal institution (especially on board a ship)  ",
      "answer": "brig"
    },
    {
      "question": "walking with slow regular strides  ",
      "answer": "pacing"
    },
    {
      "question": "catch rats, especially with dogs  ",
      "answer": "rat"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who admires a young woman",
      "answer": "admirer"
    },
    {
      "question": "loud cries made while weeping  ",
      "answer": "wailing"
    },
    {
      "question": "feelings of great warmth and intensity",
      "answer": "ardor"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a more or less disguised reference to",
      "answer": "allude"
    },
    {
      "question": "a clergyman ministering to some institution  ",
      "answer": "chaplain"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by the exactness or precision of mathematics",
      "answer": "mathematical"
    },
    {
      "question": "not to be trusted",
      "answer": "slippery"
    },
    {
      "question": "torture on the rack  ",
      "answer": "rack"
    },
    {
      "question": "stimulating or exalting to the spirit  ",
      "answer": "inspiring"
    },
    {
      "question": "in like or similar manner",
      "answer": "similarly"
    },
    {
      "question": "determine the order of constituents in",
      "answer": "sequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various game and food fishes of cool fresh waters mostly smaller than typical salmons  ",
      "answer": "trout"
    },
    {
      "question": "the first public performance of a play or movie  ",
      "answer": "premiere"
    },
    {
      "question": "situated or occurring farthest within",
      "answer": "inmost"
    },
    {
      "question": "the most powerful members of a society  ",
      "answer": "gentry"
    },
    {
      "question": "strength of mind that enables one to endure adversity with courage  ",
      "answer": "fortitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "having something on top",
      "answer": "surmounted"
    },
    {
      "question": "drawing a comparison in order to show a similarity in some respect",
      "answer": "analogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of occupying the same position or area in space",
      "answer": "coincidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "difficult to understand",
      "answer": "incomprehensible"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or pertaining to a bride",
      "answer": "bridal"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by or given to doubt",
      "answer": "doubting"
    },
    {
      "question": "agitate",
      "answer": "toss"
    },
    {
      "question": "having many complexly arranged elements",
      "answer": "intricate"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrangement of clauses in ascending order of forcefulness  ",
      "answer": "climax"
    },
    {
      "question": "become of",
      "answer": "befall"
    },
    {
      "question": "voluntary self-punishment in order to atone for some wrongdoing  ",
      "answer": "penance"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small mass of soft material",
      "answer": "wad"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by care and perseverance in carrying out tasks",
      "answer": "diligent"
    },
    {
      "question": "get or derive",
      "answer": "reap"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of being extremely abundant",
      "answer": "profusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "the practice of quoting from books or plays etc.",
      "answer": "quotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the wearing down of rock particles by friction due to water or wind or ice  ",
      "answer": "grinding"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a moral manner",
      "answer": "morally"
    },
    {
      "question": "an additional protective coating (as of paint or varnish)  ",
      "answer": "overcoat"
    },
    {
      "question": "loss of excess weight (as by dieting)",
      "answer": "reducing"
    },
    {
      "question": "take a leisurely walk",
      "answer": "promenade"
    },
    {
      "question": "the prudence and care exercised by someone in the management of resources  ",
      "answer": "providence"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being generous in behavior and temperament  ",
      "answer": "liberality"
    },
    {
      "question": "switch channels, on television  ",
      "answer": "surf"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a condition for letting out liquid drawn out as by piercing or drawing a plug",
      "answer": "tapped"
    },
    {
      "question": "swim by doing the crawl",
      "answer": "crawl"
    },
    {
      "question": "the sport of engaging in contests of speed  ",
      "answer": "racing"
    },
    {
      "question": "become soft or softer",
      "answer": "soften"
    },
    {
      "question": "a porch along the outside of a building (sometimes partly enclosed)  ",
      "answer": "veranda"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a recess in",
      "answer": "recess"
    },
    {
      "question": "many and varied",
      "answer": "manifold"
    },
    {
      "question": "not as a direct effect or consequence",
      "answer": "indirect"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving financial matters",
      "answer": "fiscal"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhale abruptly, as when one has a chest cold or congestion",
      "answer": "cough"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artful or simulated semblance",
      "answer": "guise"
    },
    {
      "question": "narrow",
      "answer": "strait"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of deceiving  ",
      "answer": "deception"
    },
    {
      "question": "study of the earth's surface",
      "answer": "geography"
    },
    {
      "question": "something (usually a supporting document) that is enclosed in an envelope with a covering letter  ",
      "answer": "enclosure"
    },
    {
      "question": "a crosspiece between the legs of a chair  ",
      "answer": "rung"
    },
    {
      "question": "rules governing socially acceptable behavior  ",
      "answer": "etiquette"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter shrill sounds",
      "answer": "crow"
    },
    {
      "question": "carve, cut, or etch into a material or surface",
      "answer": "scratch"
    },
    {
      "question": "flap the wings rapidly or fly with flapping movements",
      "answer": "flutter"
    },
    {
      "question": "made smooth by ironing  ",
      "answer": "smoothed"
    },
    {
      "question": "engaged in as a pastime",
      "answer": "amateur"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with a hood",
      "answer": "hood"
    },
    {
      "question": "the making of animated cartoons  ",
      "answer": "animation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the side or slope of a hill  ",
      "answer": "hillside"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female actor  ",
      "answer": "actress"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of changing in form or shape or appearance",
      "answer": "transformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "firm and dependable especially in loyalty",
      "answer": "steadfast"
    },
    {
      "question": "extreme greed for material wealth  ",
      "answer": "avarice"
    },
    {
      "question": "smile contemptuously",
      "answer": "sneer"
    },
    {
      "question": "being a smooth continuous motion  ",
      "answer": "sliding"
    },
    {
      "question": "clearly evident to the mind",
      "answer": "unmistakable"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing humiliation or submissiveness",
      "answer": "abject"
    },
    {
      "question": "smoothen the surface of",
      "answer": "launch"
    },
    {
      "question": "having come to an end or become void after passage of a period of time",
      "answer": "expired"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being holy  ",
      "answer": "holiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large indefinite number",
      "answer": "battalion"
    },
    {
      "question": "form a plume",
      "answer": "plume"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of not being careful or taking pains  ",
      "answer": "carelessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "making to seem more important than it really is  ",
      "answer": "exaggeration"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of singing with closed lips  ",
      "answer": "humming"
    },
    {
      "question": "the apse of a Christian church that contains the bishop's throne  ",
      "answer": "tribune"
    },
    {
      "question": "impossible to understand",
      "answer": "impenetrable"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a curiously intricate quality",
      "answer": "fanciful"
    },
    {
      "question": "deny the truth of  ",
      "answer": "contradict"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ceremonial act of clothing someone in the insignia of an office",
      "answer": "investment"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of a series of volatile hydroxyl compounds that are made from hydrocarbons by distillation  ",
      "answer": "alcohol"
    },
    {
      "question": "the appearance of things relative to one another as determined by their distance from the viewer  ",
      "answer": "perspective"
    },
    {
      "question": "a soft thin (usually translucent) paper  ",
      "answer": "tissue"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing distress or worry or anxiety",
      "answer": "distressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "become inflated",
      "answer": "balloon"
    },
    {
      "question": "explained or answered",
      "answer": "solved"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a relative manner",
      "answer": "relatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "well and tightly constructed",
      "answer": "snug"
    },
    {
      "question": "use recreational drugs  ",
      "answer": "drug"
    },
    {
      "question": "tear or be torn violently",
      "answer": "rend"
    },
    {
      "question": "cheerful compliance",
      "answer": "willingness"
    },
    {
      "question": "(formal) a person who announces important news",
      "answer": "herald"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a border especially of a specified kind",
      "answer": "bordered"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or having an unknown or unnamed source",
      "answer": "nameless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female heir  ",
      "answer": "heiress"
    },
    {
      "question": "an addictive narcotic extracted from seed capsules of the opium poppy  ",
      "answer": "opium"
    },
    {
      "question": "decorate with or as if with a surrounding fringe",
      "answer": "fringe"
    },
    {
      "question": "force to go away by blinking",
      "answer": "wink"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large mass of land projecting into a body of water  ",
      "answer": "peninsula"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert into cash",
      "answer": "redeem"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being polite and respectable  ",
      "answer": "decency"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an improper or mistaken or unfortunate manner",
      "answer": "amiss"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making a visible mark on a surface  ",
      "answer": "marking"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of arousing and holding the attention",
      "answer": "absorbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "British slang for a scolding  ",
      "answer": "wig"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt with hawks",
      "answer": "hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove the core or center from",
      "answer": "core"
    },
    {
      "question": "handwear: covers the hand and wrist  ",
      "answer": "glove"
    },
    {
      "question": "serving to instruct or enlighten or inform  ",
      "answer": "instructive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large cask especially one holding a volume equivalent to 2 butts or 252 gals  ",
      "answer": "tun"
    },
    {
      "question": "unpleasantly cold and damp",
      "answer": "bleak"
    },
    {
      "question": "adhering to ethical and moral principles",
      "answer": "ethical"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being characterized by a fixed principle or rate",
      "answer": "regularity"
    },
    {
      "question": "crowd or pack to capacity",
      "answer": "jam"
    },
    {
      "question": "respond favorably or as hoped",
      "answer": "respond"
    },
    {
      "question": "of primary import",
      "answer": "primarily"
    },
    {
      "question": "position 11 in a countable series of things  ",
      "answer": "eleventh"
    },
    {
      "question": "feel bitter or indignant about",
      "answer": "resent"
    },
    {
      "question": "believing the worst of human nature and motives",
      "answer": "cynical"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of purchasing back something previously sold  ",
      "answer": "redemption"
    },
    {
      "question": "the care (feeding and stabling) of horses for pay  ",
      "answer": "livery"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a triumphant manner",
      "answer": "triumphantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "on that",
      "answer": "thereon"
    },
    {
      "question": "radiating or as if radiating light",
      "answer": "beaming"
    },
    {
      "question": "bound with chains",
      "answer": "chained"
    },
    {
      "question": "preceding in time, order, or significance  ",
      "answer": "precedent"
    },
    {
      "question": "articles of the same kind or material",
      "answer": "ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "a class of art (or artistic endeavor) having a characteristic form or technique  ",
      "answer": "genre"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a powerful manner",
      "answer": "powerfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "pain in the head caused by dilation of cerebral arteries or muscle contractions or a reaction to drugs  ",
      "answer": "headache"
    },
    {
      "question": "the relative magnitudes of two quantities (usually expressed as a quotient)  ",
      "answer": "ratio"
    },
    {
      "question": "forming words with letters according to the principles underlying accepted usage  ",
      "answer": "spelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "intensity or forcefulness of expression",
      "answer": "vehemence"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who has lied or who lies repeatedly  ",
      "answer": "liar"
    },
    {
      "question": "readily noticed",
      "answer": "noticeable"
    },
    {
      "question": "forceful prevention",
      "answer": "suppression"
    },
    {
      "question": "appropriate for or engaged in office work",
      "answer": "clerical"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing pensive sadness",
      "answer": "pensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "holding by the police",
      "answer": "custody"
    },
    {
      "question": "cry weakly or softly",
      "answer": "wail"
    },
    {
      "question": "overly diluted",
      "answer": "watery"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tract of land used for burials  ",
      "answer": "cemetery"
    },
    {
      "question": "generous in assistance to the poor",
      "answer": "beneficent"
    },
    {
      "question": "a line of text serving to indicate what the passage below it is about",
      "answer": "heading"
    },
    {
      "question": "(finance) profits that are not paid out as dividends but are added to the capital base of the corporation  ",
      "answer": "accumulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "disabled in the feet or legs",
      "answer": "crippled"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrival that has been awaited (especially of something momentous)",
      "answer": "advent"
    },
    {
      "question": "the public performance of a sacrament or solemn ceremony with all appropriate ritual",
      "answer": "celebration"
    },
    {
      "question": "ratio of the length of the side opposite the given angle to the length of the hypotenuse of a right-angled triangle  ",
      "answer": "sine"
    },
    {
      "question": "limit in quality or quantity  ",
      "answer": "scant"
    },
    {
      "question": "comfort in disappointment or misery  ",
      "answer": "solace"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being blind or lacking sight  ",
      "answer": "blindness"
    },
    {
      "question": "copy illegally",
      "answer": "pirate"
    },
    {
      "question": "cotton trousers made of corduroy cloth  ",
      "answer": "cords"
    },
    {
      "question": "an account of the series of events making up a person's life  ",
      "answer": "biography"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a grim implacable manner",
      "answer": "grimly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a muzzle-loading shoulder gun with a long barrel",
      "answer": "musket"
    },
    {
      "question": "knitted in a loose manner",
      "answer": "loosely"
    },
    {
      "question": "the center of the Earth  ",
      "answer": "bowels"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small room (or recess) or cabinet used for storage space  ",
      "answer": "cupboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that causes or entails suffering",
      "answer": "hardship"
    },
    {
      "question": "logically valid",
      "answer": "reasoned"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone from whom you are descended (but usually more remote than a grandparent)  ",
      "answer": "ancestor"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of military officers) holding by virtue of a commission a rank of second lieutenant or ensign or above  ",
      "answer": "commissioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "a building where theatrical performances or motion-picture shows can be presented",
      "answer": "theater"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage fully",
      "answer": "consume"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjusted or attuned by adding a counterbalancing element",
      "answer": "tempered"
    },
    {
      "question": "question persistently",
      "answer": "pump"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various soft sweet desserts thickened usually with flour and baked or boiled or steamed  ",
      "answer": "pudding"
    },
    {
      "question": "able to control or determine policy",
      "answer": "controlling"
    },
    {
      "question": "underpants worn by men  ",
      "answer": "drawers"
    },
    {
      "question": "a German art song of the 19th century for voice and piano  ",
      "answer": "lied"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artist who creates sculptures  ",
      "answer": "sculptor"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used in combination) affected by something overwhelming",
      "answer": "smitten"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a rattling sound",
      "answer": "clatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "an impression that something might be the case",
      "answer": "intuition"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wrapped container  ",
      "answer": "package"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or responsible for administration  ",
      "answer": "administrative"
    },
    {
      "question": "in this place or thing or document",
      "answer": "herein"
    },
    {
      "question": "give birth to twins  ",
      "answer": "twin"
    },
    {
      "question": "having attained to kindliness or gentleness through age and experience",
      "answer": "mellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "move heavily or clumsily",
      "answer": "lumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "moor at a wharf",
      "answer": "wharf"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to the middle class  ",
      "answer": "bourgeois"
    },
    {
      "question": "away from the right path or direction",
      "answer": "astray"
    },
    {
      "question": "profoundly honored",
      "answer": "august"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who writes novels  ",
      "answer": "novelist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stupid mistake  ",
      "answer": "stupidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a generously handsome manner",
      "answer": "handsomely"
    },
    {
      "question": "temporarily incapable of speaking",
      "answer": "speechless"
    },
    {
      "question": "with that or this or it",
      "answer": "therewith"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a stern or strict bearing or demeanor",
      "answer": "austere"
    },
    {
      "question": "able to adjust readily to different conditions",
      "answer": "elastic"
    },
    {
      "question": "torture and torment like a martyr  ",
      "answer": "martyr"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of sharing in common with others (as fellows or partners etc.)  ",
      "answer": "participation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a noncommissioned officer in the Army or Air Force or Marines  ",
      "answer": "corporal"
    },
    {
      "question": "intrude in other people's affairs or business",
      "answer": "meddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "stay behind",
      "answer": "persist"
    },
    {
      "question": "having tucked or being tucked",
      "answer": "tucked"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sleeveless garment like a cloak but shorter  ",
      "answer": "cape"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cylindrical container for oxygen or compressed air  ",
      "answer": "cylinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "stupefied or dizzied by something overpowering",
      "answer": "dazzled"
    },
    {
      "question": "take a sample of",
      "answer": "sample"
    },
    {
      "question": "ruined in character or quality  ",
      "answer": "corrupted"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing lack of attention or boredom",
      "answer": "drowsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a drug that neutralizes or counteracts the effects of another drug  ",
      "answer": "antagonist"
    },
    {
      "question": "including or intended for youthful persons",
      "answer": "junior"
    },
    {
      "question": "greatly annoyed",
      "answer": "exasperated"
    },
    {
      "question": "bright and pleasant",
      "answer": "cheery"
    },
    {
      "question": "disobedient to or defiant of law",
      "answer": "lawless"
    },
    {
      "question": "direct the taking of",
      "answer": "administer"
    },
    {
      "question": "musical creation  ",
      "answer": "composing"
    },
    {
      "question": "conduct an inquiry or investigation of",
      "answer": "investigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "of very great significance",
      "answer": "momentous"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel in a caravan  ",
      "answer": "caravan"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nonmetallic bivalent element that is normally a colorless odorless tasteless nonflammable diatomic gas",
      "answer": "oxygen"
    },
    {
      "question": "one of the four playing cards in a deck that have two spots  ",
      "answer": "deuce"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or concerning or limited to a continent especially the continents of North America or Europe",
      "answer": "continental"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to court practice and procedure as opposed to the principles of law",
      "answer": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "question": "involved in a kind of operation",
      "answer": "operating"
    },
    {
      "question": "deny formally (an allegation of fact by the opposing party) in a legal suit  ",
      "answer": "traverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of having been proposed as a suitable candidate for appointment or election",
      "answer": "nomination"
    },
    {
      "question": "bring the jaws together",
      "answer": "snap"
    },
    {
      "question": "a conflict of opposed ideas or attitudes or goals",
      "answer": "collision"
    },
    {
      "question": "faithfulness and dependability in personal attachments (especially sexual fidelity)  ",
      "answer": "constancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "an open jar of glass or porcelain used as an ornament or to hold flowers  ",
      "answer": "vase"
    },
    {
      "question": "a prolonged intense look  ",
      "answer": "scrutiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "watch over",
      "answer": "overlook"
    },
    {
      "question": "large and often sumptuous tent  ",
      "answer": "pavilion"
    },
    {
      "question": "devoid of any qualifications or disguise or adornment",
      "answer": "blunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "gather (money or other resources) together over time",
      "answer": "scrape"
    },
    {
      "question": "weighing heavily on the spirit",
      "answer": "weighty"
    },
    {
      "question": "obstruct with, or as if with, a dam",
      "answer": "dam"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from control or responsibility  ",
      "answer": "unaccountable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a man who is foreperson of a jury  ",
      "answer": "foreman"
    },
    {
      "question": "the branch of military science dealing with detailed maneuvers to achieve objectives set by strategy  ",
      "answer": "tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "the utterance of sounds expressing great joy  ",
      "answer": "exultation"
    },
    {
      "question": "money or goods contributed to the poor  ",
      "answer": "alms"
    },
    {
      "question": "forceful and definite in expression or action",
      "answer": "emphatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "following immediately and as a result of what went before",
      "answer": "ensuing"
    },
    {
      "question": "beneath the surface of the sea  ",
      "answer": "submarine"
    },
    {
      "question": "of very poor quality or condition",
      "answer": "deplorable"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring at the beginning",
      "answer": "initial"
    },
    {
      "question": "become larger or bigger  ",
      "answer": "enlarge"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a physical or moral blemish so as to make impure according to dietary or ceremonial laws",
      "answer": "unclean"
    },
    {
      "question": "a point asserted as part of an argument  ",
      "answer": "contention"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by high spirits and animation  ",
      "answer": "vivacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "a textile machine having a system of revolving spikes for opening and cleaning raw textile fibers  ",
      "answer": "willow"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a dark somewhat brownish black  ",
      "answer": "sable"
    },
    {
      "question": "undergo military training or do military exercises  ",
      "answer": "drill"
    },
    {
      "question": "tested and proved to be reliable  ",
      "answer": "tested"
    },
    {
      "question": "succeed in reaching",
      "answer": "find"
    },
    {
      "question": "exerting control or influence",
      "answer": "guiding"
    },
    {
      "question": "being attentive to women like an ideal knight  ",
      "answer": "chivalrous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a science (or group of related sciences) dealing with the logic of quantity and shape and arrangement  ",
      "answer": "mathematics"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being imagined",
      "answer": "conceivable"
    },
    {
      "question": "brief and to the point",
      "answer": "crisp"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that is commanded  ",
      "answer": "commandment"
    },
    {
      "question": "plain and without any extras or adornments",
      "answer": "vanilla"
    },
    {
      "question": "negotiation between nations  ",
      "answer": "diplomacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a visible symbol representing an abstract idea  ",
      "answer": "emblem"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making a noisy disturbance  ",
      "answer": "commotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "darkened by smoke",
      "answer": "blackened"
    },
    {
      "question": "proffer (a body part)",
      "answer": "give"
    },
    {
      "question": "plain-woven cotton fabric  ",
      "answer": "muslin"
    },
    {
      "question": "skillful with the hands",
      "answer": "handy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a narrow street with walls on both sides  ",
      "answer": "alley"
    },
    {
      "question": "having scruples",
      "answer": "scrupulous"
    },
    {
      "question": "not fair",
      "answer": "unfair"
    },
    {
      "question": "a country's withdrawal from international politics",
      "answer": "isolation"
    },
    {
      "question": "receive Communion, in the Catholic church  ",
      "answer": "commune"
    },
    {
      "question": "formal or perfunctory politeness  ",
      "answer": "civility"
    },
    {
      "question": "grammatical number category referring to two or more items or units  ",
      "answer": "plural"
    },
    {
      "question": "an impudent statement  ",
      "answer": "impudence"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or revealing supreme mastery or skill",
      "answer": "consummate"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove tree stumps from",
      "answer": "stump"
    },
    {
      "question": "a liquor made from fermented mash of grain  ",
      "answer": "whiskey"
    },
    {
      "question": "with modesty",
      "answer": "modestly"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter with anger or contempt  ",
      "answer": "spit"
    },
    {
      "question": "a branch of applied mathematics concerned with the collection and interpretation of quantitative data and the use of probability theory to estimate population parameters  ",
      "answer": "statistics"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of animals) fully developed",
      "answer": "adult"
    },
    {
      "question": "avoiding waste",
      "answer": "economical"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sedimentary rock consisting mainly of calcium that was deposited by the remains of marine animals  ",
      "answer": "limestone"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with a scaffold for support",
      "answer": "scaffold"
    },
    {
      "question": "inform",
      "answer": "acquaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small pad of material that is used to protect surface from an object placed on it  ",
      "answer": "mat"
    },
    {
      "question": "study of the technique and rules for using language effectively (especially in public speaking)  ",
      "answer": "rhetoric"
    },
    {
      "question": "corresponding in function but not in evolutionary origin",
      "answer": "analogous"
    },
    {
      "question": "uninterrupted in time and indefinitely long continuing",
      "answer": "ceaseless"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of domestic animals) not selectively bred  ",
      "answer": "scrub"
    },
    {
      "question": "labored and dull",
      "answer": "ponderous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a publication that appears at fixed intervals  ",
      "answer": "periodical"
    },
    {
      "question": "move with sudden speed",
      "answer": "dart"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pale pinkish orange color  ",
      "answer": "salmon"
    },
    {
      "question": "nocturnal bird of prey with hawk-like beak and claws and large head with front-facing eyes  ",
      "answer": "owl"
    },
    {
      "question": "a trodden path  ",
      "answer": "pathway"
    },
    {
      "question": "(often followed by `of') not aware",
      "answer": "unaware"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of tempering  ",
      "answer": "temperance"
    },
    {
      "question": "cud-chewing mammal used as a draft or saddle animal in desert regions  ",
      "answer": "camel"
    },
    {
      "question": "the 22nd letter of the Greek alphabet  ",
      "answer": "chi"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being new and original (not derived from something else)  ",
      "answer": "originality"
    },
    {
      "question": "without care or thought for others",
      "answer": "thoughtless"
    },
    {
      "question": "clear of weeds",
      "answer": "weed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who rests  ",
      "answer": "rester"
    },
    {
      "question": "separate or apportion into sections",
      "answer": "partition"
    },
    {
      "question": "be shiny, as if wet",
      "answer": "glitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "made of or resembling brass (as in color or hardness)  ",
      "answer": "brazen"
    },
    {
      "question": "arranged into groups  ",
      "answer": "grouped"
    },
    {
      "question": "full of fun and high spirits",
      "answer": "playful"
    },
    {
      "question": "an implement used to propel or steer a boat  ",
      "answer": "oar"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjust through indexation",
      "answer": "index"
    },
    {
      "question": "densely populated  ",
      "answer": "populous"
    },
    {
      "question": "exude or form gum",
      "answer": "gum"
    },
    {
      "question": "drive away",
      "answer": "banish"
    },
    {
      "question": "one million million in the United States  ",
      "answer": "trillion"
    },
    {
      "question": "a high degree (of amount or force etc.)",
      "answer": "highness"
    },
    {
      "question": "at some indefinite or unstated time",
      "answer": "sometime"
    },
    {
      "question": "written formally in a large clear script, as a deed or other legal document  ",
      "answer": "engrossed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shelter serving as a place of safety or sanctuary  ",
      "answer": "haven"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone legally empowered to witness signatures and certify a document's validity and to take depositions  ",
      "answer": "notary"
    },
    {
      "question": "give a fine, sharp edge to a knife or razor  ",
      "answer": "set"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bishop of highest rank  ",
      "answer": "archbishop"
    },
    {
      "question": "a Germanic character of runic origin  ",
      "answer": "thorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "again but in a new or different way",
      "answer": "afresh"
    },
    {
      "question": "emptied or exhausted of (as by drawing off e.g. water or other liquid)",
      "answer": "drained"
    },
    {
      "question": "apart from others",
      "answer": "independently"
    },
    {
      "question": "a Spanish unit of length (about a yard) having different values in different localities  ",
      "answer": "vara"
    },
    {
      "question": "receive by genetic transmission",
      "answer": "inherit"
    },
    {
      "question": "not genuine",
      "answer": "feigned"
    },
    {
      "question": "place end to end without overlapping",
      "answer": "butt"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being qualified  ",
      "answer": "fitness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an official role",
      "answer": "officially"
    },
    {
      "question": "relatively permanent disorder of the mind  ",
      "answer": "insanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a narrow manner",
      "answer": "narrowly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is member of one's class or profession",
      "answer": "colleague"
    },
    {
      "question": "jewelry consisting of a cord or chain (often bearing gems) worn about the neck as an ornament (especially by women)  ",
      "answer": "necklace"
    },
    {
      "question": "any cedar of the genus Cedrus  ",
      "answer": "cedar"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process of the sweat glands of the skin secreting a salty fluid",
      "answer": "perspiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "treated with wax",
      "answer": "waxed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the symbol of the Democratic Party",
      "answer": "donkey"
    },
    {
      "question": "the area for food preparation on a ship  ",
      "answer": "galley"
    },
    {
      "question": "extraordinarily big or impressive",
      "answer": "thundering"
    },
    {
      "question": "a belief that rejects the orthodox tenets of a religion  ",
      "answer": "heresy"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a pattern of dots  ",
      "answer": "dotted"
    },
    {
      "question": "sow by scattering",
      "answer": "scatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "woody tropical grass having hollow woody stems",
      "answer": "bamboo"
    },
    {
      "question": "insincerity by virtue of pretending to have qualities or beliefs that you do not really have  ",
      "answer": "hypocrisy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a solemn pledge of fidelity  ",
      "answer": "plight"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being serious",
      "answer": "seriousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "mix in specific proportions",
      "answer": "gauge"
    },
    {
      "question": "a strong deep vividness of hue",
      "answer": "richness"
    },
    {
      "question": "grant a dispensation",
      "answer": "dispense"
    },
    {
      "question": "involved in difficulties  ",
      "answer": "entangled"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a hole into or between, as for ease of separation",
      "answer": "punch"
    },
    {
      "question": "state of subjection to an owner or master or forced labor imposed as punishment",
      "answer": "servitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of an enemy or one eager to fight",
      "answer": "aggressive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who breeds and cares for horses  ",
      "answer": "horseman"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of light rays) subjected to scattering by reflection from a rough surface or transmission through a translucent material",
      "answer": "diffused"
    },
    {
      "question": "the point on a curve where the tangent changes from negative on the left to positive on the right  ",
      "answer": "minimum"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a miserable manner",
      "answer": "miserably"
    },
    {
      "question": "not married or related to the unmarried state",
      "answer": "unmarried"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by skill in deception",
      "answer": "crafty"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who precedes you in time (as in holding a position or office)  ",
      "answer": "predecessor"
    },
    {
      "question": "on bad terms",
      "answer": "conflicting"
    },
    {
      "question": "forever",
      "answer": "always"
    },
    {
      "question": "part of a church divided laterally from the nave proper by rows of pillars or columns  ",
      "answer": "aisle"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a feature that helps to distinguish a person or thing",
      "answer": "distinctive"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of adjusting something to match a standard  ",
      "answer": "adjustment"
    },
    {
      "question": "break into lumps before sorting",
      "answer": "rag"
    },
    {
      "question": "any liliaceous plant of the genus Lilium having showy pendulous flowers  ",
      "answer": "lily"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who purchases and maintains an inventory of goods to be sold  ",
      "answer": "trader"
    },
    {
      "question": "at the end of each day",
      "answer": "nightly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a white sauce of fat, broth, and vegetables (used especially with braised meat)  ",
      "answer": "blanc"
    },
    {
      "question": "appointed by nomination  ",
      "answer": "nominated"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of renewing  ",
      "answer": "renewal"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking in strength or firmness or resilience",
      "answer": "limp"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a mutual or shared manner",
      "answer": "mutually"
    },
    {
      "question": "power to influence or coerce",
      "answer": "puissance"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of depriving of food or subjecting to famine",
      "answer": "starvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "abounding with or resembling stars",
      "answer": "starry"
    },
    {
      "question": "the science of mental life  ",
      "answer": "psychology"
    },
    {
      "question": "run naked in a public place  ",
      "answer": "streak"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnished with people",
      "answer": "peopled"
    },
    {
      "question": "make (one thing) compatible with (another)",
      "answer": "accommodate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lack of gratitude  ",
      "answer": "ingratitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "make noise as if chattering away",
      "answer": "chatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "an embarrassing mistake  ",
      "answer": "blunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an indignant manner",
      "answer": "indignantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a United States warship larger than a destroyer and smaller than a cruiser  ",
      "answer": "frigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "British money",
      "answer": "sterling"
    },
    {
      "question": "being favorably inclined",
      "answer": "indulgent"
    },
    {
      "question": "on a large scale without careful discrimination",
      "answer": "wholesale"
    },
    {
      "question": "forming or providing a crown or summit",
      "answer": "crowning"
    },
    {
      "question": "disposed to venture or take risks",
      "answer": "audacious"
    },
    {
      "question": "obtain by winning",
      "answer": "take"
    },
    {
      "question": "kill (animals) usually for food consumption",
      "answer": "butcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being disregarded or forgotten  ",
      "answer": "oblivion"
    },
    {
      "question": "dry (ink) with blotting paper  ",
      "answer": "blot"
    },
    {
      "question": "treatment of a specific defect",
      "answer": "correction"
    },
    {
      "question": "creating knitted wear  ",
      "answer": "knitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small replica of a person",
      "answer": "doll"
    },
    {
      "question": "not capable of being separated",
      "answer": "inseparable"
    },
    {
      "question": "be present in",
      "answer": "inhabit"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sudden attack of fear  ",
      "answer": "scare"
    },
    {
      "question": "the pursuit (of a person or animal) by following tracks or marks they left behind  ",
      "answer": "trailing"
    },
    {
      "question": "determine the amino-acid sequence of a protein during its synthesis by using information on the messenger RNA  ",
      "answer": "translate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a statute enacted by a city government  ",
      "answer": "ordinance"
    },
    {
      "question": "come down",
      "answer": "alight"
    },
    {
      "question": "walk leisurely and with no apparent aim  ",
      "answer": "stroll"
    },
    {
      "question": "attack with dogs or set dogs upon  ",
      "answer": "bait"
    },
    {
      "question": "avoid and stay away from deliberately",
      "answer": "shun"
    },
    {
      "question": "an illusory hope",
      "answer": "rainbow"
    },
    {
      "question": "make smaller or shorter",
      "answer": "telescope"
    },
    {
      "question": "wind around something in coils or loops  ",
      "answer": "coil"
    },
    {
      "question": "a trap for birds or small mammals",
      "answer": "snare"
    },
    {
      "question": "a communal village built by Indians in the southwestern United States  ",
      "answer": "pueblo"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking freshness, palatability, or showing deterioration from age",
      "answer": "stale"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small amount of solid food",
      "answer": "morsel"
    },
    {
      "question": "the person who distributes the playing cards in a card game  ",
      "answer": "dealer"
    },
    {
      "question": "turn away or aside",
      "answer": "avert"
    },
    {
      "question": "thoroughgoing",
      "answer": "downright"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musical part (vocal or instrumental) that supports or provides background for other musical parts  ",
      "answer": "accompaniment"
    },
    {
      "question": "meet at a rendezvous  ",
      "answer": "rendezvous"
    },
    {
      "question": "inclined or disposed to peace",
      "answer": "peaceable"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a satisfactory manner  ",
      "answer": "satisfactorily"
    },
    {
      "question": "not arranged in order  ",
      "answer": "disordered"
    },
    {
      "question": "a game played on ice in which heavy stones with handles are slid toward a target  ",
      "answer": "curling"
    },
    {
      "question": "providing assistance or serving a useful function  ",
      "answer": "helpful"
    },
    {
      "question": "determined by chance or impulse or whim rather than by necessity or reason",
      "answer": "capricious"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hired thug  ",
      "answer": "bully"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a deep somewhat purplish blue color similar to that of a clear October sky",
      "answer": "azure"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving risk or willingness to take a risk",
      "answer": "sporting"
    },
    {
      "question": "highly offensive",
      "answer": "disgusting"
    },
    {
      "question": "ride in or travel with a sledge",
      "answer": "sledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "formally approved and invested with legal authority  ",
      "answer": "ratified"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or derived from the sun or utilizing the energies of the sun",
      "answer": "solar"
    },
    {
      "question": "strong elastic wood of any of various ash trees",
      "answer": "ash"
    },
    {
      "question": "a function word that can be used in English to form phrasal verbs  ",
      "answer": "particle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who changes location  ",
      "answer": "traveler"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill with a stuffing while cooking",
      "answer": "farce"
    },
    {
      "question": "overbearing pride evidenced by a superior manner toward inferiors  ",
      "answer": "arrogance"
    },
    {
      "question": "a usually brief state of excitement and mental confusion often accompanied by hallucinations  ",
      "answer": "delirium"
    },
    {
      "question": "the worship given to God alone  ",
      "answer": "adoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state or fact of being an owner  ",
      "answer": "ownership"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wheeled vehicle that can be pulled by a car or truck and is equipped for occupancy  ",
      "answer": "trailer"
    },
    {
      "question": "intended or able to serve a purpose without elaboration",
      "answer": "serviceable"
    },
    {
      "question": "skillful after much practice  ",
      "answer": "practiced"
    },
    {
      "question": "at or near or toward the stern of a ship or tail of an airplane",
      "answer": "aft"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physics) a short-lived oscillation in a system caused by a sudden change of voltage or current or load  ",
      "answer": "transient"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of hair or feathers) of a golden brown to reddish brown color",
      "answer": "chestnut"
    },
    {
      "question": "be similar, be in line with  ",
      "answer": "conform"
    },
    {
      "question": "perform the services of a barber: cut the hair and/or beard of  ",
      "answer": "barber"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a uniform manner",
      "answer": "uniformly"
    },
    {
      "question": "large in number or quantity (especially of discourse)",
      "answer": "copious"
    },
    {
      "question": "alongside each other, facing in the same direction  ",
      "answer": "abreast"
    },
    {
      "question": "grow vigorously",
      "answer": "boom"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a growth of hairlike awns",
      "answer": "bearded"
    },
    {
      "question": "disclose to view as by removing a cover",
      "answer": "disclose"
    },
    {
      "question": "a deliberate act of acquisition of something, often without the permission of the owner",
      "answer": "appropriation"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artificial or unnatural or obviously contrived arrangement of details or parts etc.",
      "answer": "contrivance"
    },
    {
      "question": "not having come in contact  ",
      "answer": "untouched"
    },
    {
      "question": "the feeling that men should treat one another like brothers  ",
      "answer": "brotherhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "existing in name only",
      "answer": "nominal"
    },
    {
      "question": "material for making rails or rails collectively  ",
      "answer": "railing"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage for service under a term of contract",
      "answer": "lease"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit a three-base hit  ",
      "answer": "triple"
    },
    {
      "question": "a crisis situation or point in time when a critical decision must be made",
      "answer": "juncture"
    },
    {
      "question": "a convict who is considered trustworthy and granted special privileges  ",
      "answer": "trusty"
    },
    {
      "question": "preceding and preparing for something",
      "answer": "preparatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a vibrator consisting of a thin strip of stiff material that vibrates to produce a tone when air streams over it",
      "answer": "reed"
    },
    {
      "question": "practices that are handed down from the past by tradition",
      "answer": "heritage"
    },
    {
      "question": "boldly resisting authority or an opposing force",
      "answer": "defiant"
    },
    {
      "question": "a structure that has been erected  ",
      "answer": "erection"
    },
    {
      "question": "exceptionally",
      "answer": "uncommonly"
    },
    {
      "question": "happiness with one's situation in life  ",
      "answer": "contentment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a primitive method of determining a person's guilt or innocence by subjecting the accused person to dangerous or painful tests believed to be under divine control",
      "answer": "ordeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Old World vine with lobed evergreen leaves and black berrylike fruits  ",
      "answer": "ivy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the periodic passage of groups of animals (especially birds or fishes) from one region to another for feeding or breeding  ",
      "answer": "migration"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used in combination) having the odor of",
      "answer": "scented"
    },
    {
      "question": "take solid or liquid food into the mouth a little at a time either by drinking or by eating with a spoon  ",
      "answer": "sup"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking stimulating characteristics",
      "answer": "bland"
    },
    {
      "question": "worthy of reliance or trust",
      "answer": "reliable"
    },
    {
      "question": "submissive or fawning in attitude or behavior",
      "answer": "servile"
    },
    {
      "question": "uncommonly early or before the expected time",
      "answer": "premature"
    },
    {
      "question": "thrown together in a disorderly fashion",
      "answer": "scrambled"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking warmth of feeling",
      "answer": "chilly"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or belonging to or inherited from an ancestor  ",
      "answer": "ancestral"
    },
    {
      "question": "poorly articulated or enunciated, or drowned by noise",
      "answer": "unintelligible"
    },
    {
      "question": "fixed and absolute and without contingency",
      "answer": "vested"
    },
    {
      "question": "bind with a rope, chain, or cord",
      "answer": "lash"
    },
    {
      "question": "devoid of courage or enthusiasm  ",
      "answer": "heartless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pleasingly sweet olfactory property  ",
      "answer": "bouquet"
    },
    {
      "question": "low-lying wet land with grassy vegetation",
      "answer": "marsh"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a senate  ",
      "answer": "senator"
    },
    {
      "question": "tell or spread rumors",
      "answer": "rumor"
    },
    {
      "question": "sexually exciting or gratifying",
      "answer": "sensual"
    },
    {
      "question": "befitting or characteristic of a woman especially a mature woman",
      "answer": "womanly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the date on which an obligation must be repaid  ",
      "answer": "maturity"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with a berth  ",
      "answer": "berth"
    },
    {
      "question": "march in protest",
      "answer": "demonstrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing or characterized by error",
      "answer": "erroneous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a proportion in relation to a whole (which is usually the amount per hundred)  ",
      "answer": "percentage"
    },
    {
      "question": "enter into a calendar  ",
      "answer": "calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of nourishing",
      "answer": "nourishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an imperfect or faulty way",
      "answer": "imperfectly"
    },
    {
      "question": "damaged by decay",
      "answer": "decayed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a Gestalt principle of organization holding that (other things being equal) parts of a stimulus field that are similar to each other tend to be perceived as belonging together as a unit  ",
      "answer": "similarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "not important",
      "answer": "unimportant"
    },
    {
      "question": "clean one's body by immersion into water",
      "answer": "bathe"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of signing your name",
      "answer": "subscription"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or concerned with electricity",
      "answer": "electrical"
    },
    {
      "question": "management by overseeing the performance or operation of a person or group  ",
      "answer": "supervision"
    },
    {
      "question": "annual native to South America having underground stolons bearing edible starchy tubers",
      "answer": "potato"
    },
    {
      "question": "difficult to accomplish",
      "answer": "arduous"
    },
    {
      "question": "as if squeezed uncomfortably tight",
      "answer": "pinched"
    },
    {
      "question": "affectionate play (or foreplay without contact with the genital organs)  ",
      "answer": "caressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to move or pass silently, smoothly, or imperceptibly  ",
      "answer": "glide"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who enjoys taking risks  ",
      "answer": "adventurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "decide as to where something belongs in a scheme",
      "answer": "assign"
    },
    {
      "question": "introduced into as a part of the whole",
      "answer": "incorporated"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by imagination, initiative, and readiness to undertake new projects",
      "answer": "enterprising"
    },
    {
      "question": "completely obstructed or closed off",
      "answer": "blocked"
    },
    {
      "question": "playful in an appealingly bold way",
      "answer": "devilish"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or pertaining to the art and science of architecture",
      "answer": "architectural"
    },
    {
      "question": "look over carefully",
      "answer": "inspect"
    },
    {
      "question": "a depository for collecting and displaying objects having scientific or historical or artistic value  ",
      "answer": "museum"
    },
    {
      "question": "gather nuts  ",
      "answer": "nut"
    },
    {
      "question": "sell or provide on credit  ",
      "answer": "finance"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by skill in achieving a desired end especially with cunning or craft",
      "answer": "artful"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who journeys to a sacred place as an act of religious devotion  ",
      "answer": "pilgrim"
    },
    {
      "question": "cooked by frying in fat  ",
      "answer": "fried"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an extremely intelligent way",
      "answer": "brilliantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "gathered for protruding fullness",
      "answer": "puff"
    },
    {
      "question": "as if under the influence of alcohol",
      "answer": "intoxicated"
    },
    {
      "question": "trap with a snare",
      "answer": "gin"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unjust manner",
      "answer": "unjustly"
    },
    {
      "question": "affording comfort or solace  ",
      "answer": "comforting"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who performs magic tricks to amuse an audience  ",
      "answer": "magician"
    },
    {
      "question": "still in existence",
      "answer": "surviving"
    },
    {
      "question": "lose the lead  ",
      "answer": "exit"
    },
    {
      "question": "inquiring or appearing to inquire",
      "answer": "inquisitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "an abstracted state of absorption  ",
      "answer": "reverie"
    },
    {
      "question": "desperate recklessness",
      "answer": "desperation"
    },
    {
      "question": "forage food  ",
      "answer": "rustle"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to persuade by forcefulness of argument",
      "answer": "compelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut and spread open, as in preparation for cooking",
      "answer": "butterfly"
    },
    {
      "question": "connected by a link, as railway cars or trailer trucks  ",
      "answer": "coupled"
    },
    {
      "question": "set the level or character of",
      "answer": "gear"
    },
    {
      "question": "a detailed account or description of something",
      "answer": "recital"
    },
    {
      "question": "be the source of pain  ",
      "answer": "ache"
    },
    {
      "question": "the physical composition of something (especially with respect to the size and shape of the small constituents of a substance)",
      "answer": "texture"
    },
    {
      "question": "a temporary debarment (from a privilege or position etc)  ",
      "answer": "suspension"
    },
    {
      "question": "adroitness in using the hands  ",
      "answer": "dexterity"
    },
    {
      "question": "not customary or usual",
      "answer": "unaccustomed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of the British order of honor",
      "answer": "baronet"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being held in high esteem and honor  ",
      "answer": "repute"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking justification or authorization",
      "answer": "undue"
    },
    {
      "question": "in several ways",
      "answer": "multiply"
    },
    {
      "question": "the status of a woman  ",
      "answer": "womanhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "walk clumsily  ",
      "answer": "clump"
    },
    {
      "question": "collection of costumes belonging to a theatrical company  ",
      "answer": "wardrobe"
    },
    {
      "question": "a boat propelled by a steam engine  ",
      "answer": "steamboat"
    },
    {
      "question": "the status of belonging to a particular nation by birth or naturalization  ",
      "answer": "nationality"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being difficult to do",
      "answer": "hardness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a copy made with carbon paper  ",
      "answer": "carbon"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of failure or error",
      "answer": "infallible"
    },
    {
      "question": "fearfulness in venturing into new and unknown places or activities  ",
      "answer": "timidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "conforming to truth",
      "answer": "truthful"
    },
    {
      "question": "pH value of 7  ",
      "answer": "neutrality"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unconcerned manner",
      "answer": "casually"
    },
    {
      "question": "not capable of being obtained",
      "answer": "inaccessible"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a beastly manner",
      "answer": "beastly"
    },
    {
      "question": "out of the ordinary",
      "answer": "unwonted"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a very dark grey  ",
      "answer": "charcoal"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a peaceful manner",
      "answer": "peacefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a category of poetry that expresses emotion (often in a songlike way)",
      "answer": "lyric"
    },
    {
      "question": "be lively or brilliant or exhibit virtuosity",
      "answer": "sparkle"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause annoyance in",
      "answer": "annoy"
    },
    {
      "question": "an administrative division of a county",
      "answer": "township"
    },
    {
      "question": "auguring favorable circumstances and good luck",
      "answer": "auspicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "create by organizing and linking ideas, arguments, or concepts",
      "answer": "construct"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman in charge of nursing in a medical institution  ",
      "answer": "matron"
    },
    {
      "question": "punish severely",
      "answer": "scourge"
    },
    {
      "question": "the feeling of being displeased and discontent",
      "answer": "dissatisfaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter rapidly",
      "answer": "volley"
    },
    {
      "question": "flesh of chickens or turkeys or ducks or geese raised for food  ",
      "answer": "poultry"
    },
    {
      "question": "cross a river where it's shallow  ",
      "answer": "ford"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat in a tank",
      "answer": "tank"
    },
    {
      "question": "the voluntary surrender of property (or a right to property) without attempting to reclaim it or give it away  ",
      "answer": "abandonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "that is on a string",
      "answer": "strung"
    },
    {
      "question": "the 14th letter of the Greek alphabet  ",
      "answer": "xi"
    },
    {
      "question": "outlying areas (as of a city or town)",
      "answer": "outskirts"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stable order (especially of society)  ",
      "answer": "stability"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing many mountains  ",
      "answer": "mountainous"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of the larger branches of a tree  ",
      "answer": "bough"
    },
    {
      "question": "fortification consisting of a low wall  ",
      "answer": "parapet"
    },
    {
      "question": "not known or well known",
      "answer": "unfamiliar"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small apparently simple structure (as a fertilized egg) from which new tissue can develop into a complete organism  ",
      "answer": "germ"
    },
    {
      "question": "open up and explore a new area",
      "answer": "pioneer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a specially long, formal letter  ",
      "answer": "epistle"
    },
    {
      "question": "plan in detail",
      "answer": "chart"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who makes things  ",
      "answer": "maker"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or showing feelings of unwarranted importance out of overbearing pride",
      "answer": "arrogant"
    },
    {
      "question": "caused to abandon an evil manner of living and follow a good one",
      "answer": "reformed"
    },
    {
      "question": "shining unsteadily  ",
      "answer": "flickering"
    },
    {
      "question": "toasted or roasted slightly",
      "answer": "parched"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or showing no mercy",
      "answer": "merciless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a high ranking police officer  ",
      "answer": "inspector"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing concern for the rights and feelings of others",
      "answer": "considerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "not secure",
      "answer": "precarious"
    },
    {
      "question": "a monastery ruled by an abbot  ",
      "answer": "abbey"
    },
    {
      "question": "hurl or throw violently",
      "answer": "precipitate"
    },
    {
      "question": "rock that in its molten form (as magma) issues from volcanos",
      "answer": "lava"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small coin of the United Kingdom worth six pennies",
      "answer": "sixpence"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of tumors, e.g.) slow to heal or develop and usually painless",
      "answer": "indolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "carry in a bucket  ",
      "answer": "bucket"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover or traverse by taking long steps",
      "answer": "stride"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who pays for goods or services  ",
      "answer": "customer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a high standing achieved through success or influence or wealth etc.",
      "answer": "prestige"
    },
    {
      "question": "protect from impact",
      "answer": "cushion"
    },
    {
      "question": "block the action of  ",
      "answer": "repress"
    },
    {
      "question": "the statement of a theme in notes of lesser duration (usually half the length of the original)  ",
      "answer": "diminution"
    },
    {
      "question": "prolong or extend",
      "answer": "spin"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stopping",
      "answer": "cessation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of one mind",
      "answer": "unanimously"
    },
    {
      "question": "work as the skipper on a vessel  ",
      "answer": "skipper"
    },
    {
      "question": "the date on which an event occurred in some previous year (or the celebration of it)  ",
      "answer": "anniversary"
    },
    {
      "question": "a playing field where sports events take place  ",
      "answer": "arena"
    },
    {
      "question": "more desirable than another",
      "answer": "preferable"
    },
    {
      "question": "an antiquity that has survived from the distant past  ",
      "answer": "relic"
    },
    {
      "question": "wrongly understood",
      "answer": "misunderstood"
    },
    {
      "question": "composed of a dense cluster of separate units such as carpels or florets or drupelets",
      "answer": "aggregate"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of being placated",
      "answer": "implacable"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt frogs for food  ",
      "answer": "frog"
    },
    {
      "question": "lying beyond what is openly revealed or avowed (especially being kept in the background or deliberately concealed)",
      "answer": "subterranean"
    },
    {
      "question": "not capable of being carried out or put into practice",
      "answer": "impracticable"
    },
    {
      "question": "not conveniently timed",
      "answer": "inconvenient"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of being entirely consumed or used up",
      "answer": "inexhaustible"
    },
    {
      "question": "the source of an artist's inspiration",
      "answer": "muse"
    },
    {
      "question": "having confidence restored",
      "answer": "reassured"
    },
    {
      "question": "a light shower that falls in some locations and not others nearby  ",
      "answer": "scattering"
    },
    {
      "question": "a system considered analogous in structure or function to a living body",
      "answer": "organism"
    },
    {
      "question": "such that comparison is impossible",
      "answer": "incomparable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dark oil consisting mainly of hydrocarbons  ",
      "answer": "petroleum"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who composes music as a profession  ",
      "answer": "composer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the practice of measuring angles and distances on the ground so that they can be accurately plotted on a map",
      "answer": "surveying"
    },
    {
      "question": "smoothen and neaten with or as with a comb",
      "answer": "comb"
    },
    {
      "question": "to so extreme a degree",
      "answer": "such"
    },
    {
      "question": "make illegal payments to in exchange for favors or influence",
      "answer": "bribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "spend or take a vacation  ",
      "answer": "vacation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of steering a ship  ",
      "answer": "steering"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making something clean",
      "answer": "cleaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "a male member of a religious order that originally relied solely on alms  ",
      "answer": "friar"
    },
    {
      "question": "skin of a sheep or goat prepared for writing on  ",
      "answer": "parchment"
    },
    {
      "question": "to such an extent or degree",
      "answer": "insomuch"
    },
    {
      "question": "affect as in thought or feeling",
      "answer": "tinge"
    },
    {
      "question": "detached by cutting",
      "answer": "severed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a colorless volatile highly inflammable liquid formerly used as an inhalation anesthetic  ",
      "answer": "ether"
    },
    {
      "question": "without scruples or principles",
      "answer": "unscrupulous"
    },
    {
      "question": "can be felt by palpation",
      "answer": "palpable"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of correcting an error or a fault or an evil  ",
      "answer": "redress"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Church of England) a clergyman appointed to act as priest of a parish  ",
      "answer": "vicar"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quotient of two rational numbers  ",
      "answer": "fraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "not greedy  ",
      "answer": "unselfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "required by rule",
      "answer": "compulsory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a reference book containing an alphabetical list of words with information about them  ",
      "answer": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with power and authority",
      "answer": "invest"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of transferring property title from one person to another  ",
      "answer": "conveyance"
    },
    {
      "question": "neglecting to do something",
      "answer": "omission"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a vehement manner",
      "answer": "vehemently"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover as if with clothing",
      "answer": "clothe"
    },
    {
      "question": "producing or covered with lathery sweat or saliva from exhaustion or disease",
      "answer": "foaming"
    },
    {
      "question": "effort expended in moving one object over another with pressure  ",
      "answer": "friction"
    },
    {
      "question": "do away with",
      "answer": "abolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "provoking horror",
      "answer": "atrocious"
    },
    {
      "question": "a Gestalt principle of organization holding that (other things being equal) objects or events that are near to one another (in space or time) are perceived as belonging together as a unit  ",
      "answer": "proximity"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of relying on something  ",
      "answer": "reliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "full of the sound of voices",
      "answer": "vocal"
    },
    {
      "question": "choose not to consume",
      "answer": "abstain"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to spread in another part of the world",
      "answer": "export"
    },
    {
      "question": "(antiquity) a wreath of laurel foliage worn on the head as an emblem of victory  ",
      "answer": "laurel"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a groove in  ",
      "answer": "rout"
    },
    {
      "question": "represent in profile, by drawing or painting  ",
      "answer": "profile"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a flower or bloom",
      "answer": "flowering"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making a sudden noisy break  ",
      "answer": "rupture"
    },
    {
      "question": "press firmly",
      "answer": "squeeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short labored intake of breath with the mouth open",
      "answer": "gasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a crew",
      "answer": "manned"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage in a mutiny against an authority  ",
      "answer": "mutiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "greatly desired  ",
      "answer": "coveted"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sign of something about to happen",
      "answer": "omen"
    },
    {
      "question": "showy American butterfly resembling the monarch but smaller  ",
      "answer": "viceroy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of extinguishing",
      "answer": "extinction"
    },
    {
      "question": "with persistence  ",
      "answer": "persistently"
    },
    {
      "question": "the termination of drug taking  ",
      "answer": "withdrawal"
    },
    {
      "question": "stir with a paddle  ",
      "answer": "paddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fixed number of lines of verse forming a unit of a poem  ",
      "answer": "stanza"
    },
    {
      "question": "used especially of persons",
      "answer": "stalwart"
    },
    {
      "question": "a linear unit (1/40 inch) used to measure diameter of buttons  ",
      "answer": "ligne"
    },
    {
      "question": "deeply or completely",
      "answer": "soundly"
    },
    {
      "question": "impelled by physical force especially against resistance",
      "answer": "forcible"
    },
    {
      "question": "acting with uncertainty or hesitance or lack of confidence",
      "answer": "groping"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of plans, ideas, etc.) perfectly formed",
      "answer": "perfected"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an active manner",
      "answer": "actively"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert (from an investment trust to a unit trust)  ",
      "answer": "utilize"
    },
    {
      "question": "carrying developing offspring within the body or being about to produce new life  ",
      "answer": "pregnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by a disposition to oppose and contradict",
      "answer": "perverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) a listing of the files stored in memory (usually on a hard disk)  ",
      "answer": "directory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a skillet made of cast iron  ",
      "answer": "spider"
    },
    {
      "question": "a character set that includes letters and is used to write a language  ",
      "answer": "alphabet"
    },
    {
      "question": "clothe formally",
      "answer": "vest"
    },
    {
      "question": "the business of drawing public attention to goods and services  ",
      "answer": "advertising"
    },
    {
      "question": "superficially attractive and stylish",
      "answer": "glossy"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of hair) having curls or waves",
      "answer": "curly"
    },
    {
      "question": "not of the nobility",
      "answer": "ignoble"
    },
    {
      "question": "(usually in the plural) trousers made of flannel or gabardine or tweed or white cloth  ",
      "answer": "flannel"
    },
    {
      "question": "still legally acceptable",
      "answer": "valid"
    },
    {
      "question": "having one or more incisions reaching nearly to the midrib  ",
      "answer": "cleft"
    },
    {
      "question": "knowledge gained through tradition or anecdote",
      "answer": "lore"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of neglecting responsibilities and lacking concern  ",
      "answer": "negligence"
    },
    {
      "question": "the sexual activity of conceiving and bearing offspring  ",
      "answer": "reproduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "to, toward, or in the northwest  ",
      "answer": "northwest"
    },
    {
      "question": "transport by barge on a body of water  ",
      "answer": "barge"
    },
    {
      "question": "taking responsibility for one's conduct and obligations",
      "answer": "trustworthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by pomp or ceremony or formality",
      "answer": "ceremonial"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a moderate degree",
      "answer": "mildly"
    },
    {
      "question": "improvement (or an intended improvement) in the existing form or condition of institutions or practices etc.",
      "answer": "reformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or showing a feeling of mixed reverence and respect and wonder and dread",
      "answer": "awed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who gives up too easily  ",
      "answer": "quitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "providence by virtue of planning prudently for the future  ",
      "answer": "foresight"
    },
    {
      "question": "sealed vessel where water is converted to steam  ",
      "answer": "boiler"
    },
    {
      "question": "the discovery and description of the course of development of something",
      "answer": "tracing"
    },
    {
      "question": "much greater than the normal",
      "answer": "abnormal"
    },
    {
      "question": "done or happening at the appropriate or proper time",
      "answer": "timely"
    },
    {
      "question": "(logic) an attribute of a logical system that is so constituted that none of the propositions deducible from the axioms contradict one another  ",
      "answer": "consistency"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who inhabits a particular place  ",
      "answer": "inhabitant"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with a canopy  ",
      "answer": "canopy"
    },
    {
      "question": "plaster with mortar",
      "answer": "mortar"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an intimately familiar manner",
      "answer": "familiarly"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by keen caution and watchful prudence",
      "answer": "wary"
    },
    {
      "question": "be or work as an apprentice",
      "answer": "apprentice"
    },
    {
      "question": "penetrate or assault, in a harmful or injurious way",
      "answer": "invade"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who helps people or institutions (especially with financial help)  ",
      "answer": "benefactor"
    },
    {
      "question": "an outstanding achievement  ",
      "answer": "masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "extract (metals) by heating  ",
      "answer": "smelt"
    },
    {
      "question": "the degree of visibility of your environment  ",
      "answer": "illumination"
    },
    {
      "question": "wear away or erode  ",
      "answer": "fret"
    },
    {
      "question": "search for something needed or desired",
      "answer": "raid"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act or process of changing the color of something  ",
      "answer": "coloring"
    },
    {
      "question": "fit with a muzzle",
      "answer": "muzzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of movement) slow and laborious",
      "answer": "leaden"
    }
  ]
}